Since I was ordered to find the lost stars
to save the Divine Clan from its collapsing fate,
it has been a hundred years.
But there is still no clue about the whereabouts of the last star.
Please guide me, Divine Envoy.
Tang Zhiluo.
A wise ruler has been born.
You must go to his side
and help him become a great ruler.
Only then can you obtain the star
and complete your mission.
I have sealed your magic.
Your combat power is only slightly higher than an ordinary person's.
You still need to rely on your wits.
Who are you?
Who exactly are you?
Give it back to me.
I am here to assist you in becoming a wise ruler.
If you could really go back,
there wouldn't have been that scam just now.
Since you can't go home now anyway,
why not take me as your master
and learn some real skills from me?
If you don't speak,
I'll take it as a yes.
Here, a welcome gift from your master.
Here, be careful of the bones.
Jingzhou was well managed.
My father intends to name an heir and ordered me back.
That's a good thing.
Let's pack our things
and leave immediately.
I've been in touch with the capital,
but I didn't tell you.
You don't blame me?
It's your strategy.
Why would I blame you?
But I don't want to go back now.
Why?
You have so many skills now.
If you don't return to the capital,
how will you use them?
I just feel
living here with you is quite nice.
Excuse me, does Prince Shuo live here?
You have been away from the capital for a year, Your Highness.
Seeing this scenery,
what are your thoughts?
Sacrificing to heaven and earth with elegance,
a mortal dragon is not what I desire.
Miss Tang, have you found anything?
The terrain here is complex.
It's very easy to hide after dark,
making it an excellent place for an ambush.
Are you okay?
Judging by their moves, they look like assassins raised by Jingzhou.
We can't leave unless we kill them all.
His Highness hasn't even reached the capital's gates,
yet the assassins have already caught up.
It seems we must not show any mercy upon returning to the capital.